

12 rue des Violettes 31570 BOURG SAINT BERNARD Permis B, Véhiculé

+33 6 78 61 47 00

magnan.fabrice@gmail.com

https://portfolio.fabwebprojects.fr/

in fabrice-magnan-de-bellevue

Fabrice-Perso

#### Degrees and Certifications

2024: "Web Integrator" Diploma, OpenClassroom (Equivalent to 2 years of higher education)

2018: SQL Server Training, SQL Programming, Orsys Training

2018: VBA EXCEL Training, FortimeLp

2008: University Technology Diploma in Business and Administration Management, Finance-Accounting Major, Perpignan

# Languages

French: Mother Languages

English: Professionnel

# Hobbies

Development of personal web projects and technological monitoring.

**Enthusiast of American** motorcycles, with a marked interest in the culture and history of the United States, enriching my taste for travel.

Movie and TV series fan, with a particular interest in the culture and history of the United States.

#### Fabrice MAGNAN de BELLEVUE

## Full Stack Web Developer

#### Introduction

As a web developer specialized in **React** and **PHP** with 3 years of experience, I come from a strong background in computer science that has guided my career transition towards my passion for web development. Agile in problem-solving and innovation, I am committed to creating effective, user-centered web solutions. My journey is marked by constant evolution and a pursuit of technological excellence.

# Professional Experiences

### Septeo ADB (Groupe Septeo) 2021 to 07/2023 - Developer

- Development and maintenance of a website for entering and integrating configuration questionnaires in HTML/PHP/JS linked to a MySQL database.
- Linking the questionnaire to a data migration tool in VB.NET/SQL Server.
- Participating in the update and correction of existing tools in VB.NET, with the support of experienced developers.
- Participation in Agile method sprints

#### 09/2016 to 07/2023 - Technical Referent, Migration Technician, Procedure Writer 11/2013 to 09/2016 - Support Technician

- Development in VBA Excel to automate accounting checks related to migration tasks.
- Writer of procedures, technical documents.

## **Previous Support Experiences**

Between 2008 and 2013 - Business and technical support

- Provided business and technical support for a variety of accountingoriented software.
- Employer: ComputaCenter, SCC, and Magnus.
- Ability to simplify and communicate complex solutions to a diverse audience.
- Adaptation to users' needs to provide effective and personalized technical support.

## Skills Skills































# Soft Skills

- Collaboration and Communication
- Creative Problem Solving
- Adaptability and Innovation
- Curiosity and Passion for Technology